WJZ-TV Collection R0129.WJZ R0129.WJZ
Stage
- Evening Magazine, 1977-1991; EVMAG; 8 Reels 2 inch videotape: Quad; 4,676 Cassettes
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-17; WJZ-EVMAG-180-016 (Mixed materials 180, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-17; WJZ-EVMAG-180-017 (Mixed materials 180, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-19-1990-03-22; WJZ-EVMAG-180-018 (Mixed materials 180, Tape 18)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-19-1990-03-20; WJZ-EVMAG-181-001 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-20-1990-03-21; WJZ-EVMAG-181-002 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-20; WJZ-EVMAG-181-003 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-20; WJZ-EVMAG-181-004 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-21; WJZ-EVMAG-181-005 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-21; WJZ-EVMAG-181-006 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-28; WJZ-EVMAG-181-007 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-22-1990-03-23; WJZ-EVMAG-181-008 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-26-1990-03-30; WJZ-EVMAG-181-009 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-26; WJZ-EVMAG-181-010 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-23; WJZ-EVMAG-181-011 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-26; WJZ-EVMAG-181-012 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-28; WJZ-EVMAG-181-013 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-30; WJZ-EVMAG-181-014 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-30; WJZ-EVMAG-181-015 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04; WJZ-EVMAG-181-016 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-02; WJZ-EVMAG-181-017 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-02-1990-04-03; WJZ-EVMAG-181-018 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 18)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-03; WJZ-EVMAG-181-019 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 19)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-03; WJZ-EVMAG-181-020 (Mixed materials 181, Tape 20)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-04; WJZ-EVMAG-182-001 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-06; WJZ-EVMAG-182-002 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-09; WJZ-EVMAG-182-003 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-10; WJZ-EVMAG-182-004 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-11; WJZ-EVMAG-182-005 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-12; WJZ-EVMAG-182-006 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-13; WJZ-EVMAG-182-007 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-14; WJZ-EVMAG-182-008 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-03-07; WJZ-EVMAG-182-009 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-16; WJZ-EVMAG-182-010 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-17; WJZ-EVMAG-182-011 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-18; WJZ-EVMAG-182-012 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-19; WJZ-EVMAG-182-013 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-20; WJZ-EVMAG-182-014 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-23; WJZ-EVMAG-182-015 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-24; WJZ-EVMAG-182-016 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-04-25; WJZ-EVMAG-182-017 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-05; WJZ-EVMAG-182-018 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 18)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-05-08; WJZ-EVMAG-182-019 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 19)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-05-10; WJZ-EVMAG-182-020 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 20)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-05-14-1990-05-15; WJZ-EVMAG-182-021 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 21)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-05-28; WJZ-EVMAG-182-022 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 22)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-05-30; WJZ-EVMAG-182-023 (Mixed materials 182, Tape 23)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-01; WJZ-EVMAG-183-001 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-11; WJZ-EVMAG-183-002 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-12; WJZ-EVMAG-183-003 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-07; WJZ-EVMAG-183-004 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-08; WJZ-EVMAG-183-005 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-08; WJZ-EVMAG-183-006 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-14; WJZ-EVMAG-183-007 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-18; WJZ-EVMAG-183-008 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-19; WJZ-EVMAG-183-009 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-20; WJZ-EVMAG-183-010 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-21; WJZ-EVMAG-183-011 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-22; WJZ-EVMAG-183-012 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-25; WJZ-EVMAG-183-013 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-26; WJZ-EVMAG-183-014 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-06-28; WJZ-EVMAG-183-015 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-07-02; WJZ-EVMAG-183-016 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-07-05; WJZ-EVMAG-183-017 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-07-06; WJZ-EVMAG-183-018 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 18)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-07-09; WJZ-EVMAG-183-019 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 19)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-07-10; WJZ-EVMAG-183-020 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 20)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-183-021 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 21)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-07-21; WJZ-EVMAG-183-022 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 22)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-07-24; WJZ-EVMAG-183-023 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 23)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-07-25; WJZ-EVMAG-183-024 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 24)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-07-25-1990-07-26; WJZ-EVMAG-183-025 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 25)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-07-27-1990-07-30; WJZ-EVMAG-183-026 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 26)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-07-31; WJZ-EVMAG-183-027 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 27)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-01; WJZ-EVMAG-183-028 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 28)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-02; WJZ-EVMAG-183-029 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 29)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-03; WJZ-EVMAG-183-030 (Mixed materials 183, Tape 30)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-06; WJZ-EVMAG-184-001 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-07; WJZ-EVMAG-184-002 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-09; WJZ-EVMAG-184-003 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-10; WJZ-EVMAG-184-004 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-14; WJZ-EVMAG-184-005 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-16; WJZ-EVMAG-184-006 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-17; WJZ-EVMAG-184-007 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-20-1990-08-21; WJZ-EVMAG-184-008 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-21; WJZ-EVMAG-184-009 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-23; WJZ-EVMAG-184-010 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-27; WJZ-EVMAG-184-011 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-08-31; WJZ-EVMAG-184-012 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-03; WJZ-EVMAG-184-013 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-04; WJZ-EVMAG-184-014 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-05; WJZ-EVMAG-184-015 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-06; WJZ-EVMAG-184-016 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-13; WJZ-EVMAG-184-017 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-14; WJZ-EVMAG-184-018 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 18)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-20; WJZ-EVMAG-184-019 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 19)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-17; WJZ-EVMAG-184-020 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 20)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-21; WJZ-EVMAG-184-021 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 21)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-24; WJZ-EVMAG-184-022 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 22)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-25; WJZ-EVMAG-184-023 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 23)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-26; WJZ-EVMAG-184-024 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 24)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-27; WJZ-EVMAG-184-025 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 25)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-09-28; WJZ-EVMAG-184-026 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 26)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-01; WJZ-EVMAG-184-027 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 27)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-02; WJZ-EVMAG-184-028 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 28)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-03; WJZ-EVMAG-184-029 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 29)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-04; WJZ-EVMAG-184-030 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 30)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-08; WJZ-EVMAG-184-031 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 31)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-12; WJZ-EVMAG-184-032 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 32)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-16; WJZ-EVMAG-184-033 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 33)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-17; WJZ-EVMAG-184-034 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 34)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-18; WJZ-EVMAG-184-035 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 35)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-19; WJZ-EVMAG-184-036 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 36)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-22; WJZ-EVMAG-184-037 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 37)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-24; WJZ-EVMAG-184-038 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 38)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-26; WJZ-EVMAG-184-039 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 39)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-29; WJZ-EVMAG-184-040 (Mixed materials 184, Tape 40)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-29-1990-10-30; WJZ-EVMAG-185-001 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-30; WJZ-EVMAG-185-002 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-02; WJZ-EVMAG-185-003 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-05; WJZ-EVMAG-185-004 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-06; WJZ-EVMAG-185-005 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-08; WJZ-EVMAG-185-006 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-10-25; WJZ-EVMAG-185-007 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-09; WJZ-EVMAG-185-008 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-12; WJZ-EVMAG-185-009 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-14; WJZ-EVMAG-185-010 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-15; WJZ-EVMAG-185-011 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-16; WJZ-EVMAG-185-012 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-19; WJZ-EVMAG-185-013 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-20; WJZ-EVMAG-185-014 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-22; WJZ-EVMAG-185-015 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-23; WJZ-EVMAG-185-016 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-26; WJZ-EVMAG-185-017 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-27; WJZ-EVMAG-185-018 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 18)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-28; WJZ-EVMAG-185-019 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 19)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-11-29; WJZ-EVMAG-185-020 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 20)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-12-03; WJZ-EVMAG-185-021 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 21)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-12-04; WJZ-EVMAG-185-022 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 22)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-12-06; WJZ-EVMAG-185-023 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 23)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-12-07; WJZ-EVMAG-185-024 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 24)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-12-10; WJZ-EVMAG-185-025 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 25)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-12-11; WJZ-EVMAG-185-026 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 26)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-12-12; WJZ-EVMAG-185-027 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 27)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-12-13; WJZ-EVMAG-185-028 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 28)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-12-14; WJZ-EVMAG-185-029 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 29)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-12-18; WJZ-EVMAG-185-030 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 30)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-12-21; WJZ-EVMAG-185-031 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 31)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-29; WJZ-EVMAG-185-032 (Mixed materials 185, Tape 32)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-11-18-1977-12-07; WJZ-EVMAG-006-012 (Mixed materials 6, Tape 12)
    - Love Boat Captain, 1977-11-18; WJZ-EVMAG-006-012-001 (Mixed materials 6, Tape 12, Segment 1)
    - Gonged to Reisterstown, 1977-12-07; WJZ-EVMAG-006-012-002 (Mixed materials 6, Tape 12, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-12-07; WJZ-EVMAG-006-013 (Mixed materials x, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-11-23; WJZ-EVMAG-006-017 (Mixed materials 6, Tape 16)
    - I Proved I'm Not Crazy, 1977-11-23; WJZ-EVMAG-006-017-001 (Mixed materials 6, Tape 16, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-11-21; WJZ-EVMAG-006-014 (Mixed materials 6, Tape 13)
    - Monte Rock, 1977-11-21; WJZ-EVMAG-006-017-001 (Mixed materials 6, Tape 13, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-11-22; WJZ-EVMAG-006-016 (Mixed materials 6, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-11-21; WJZ-EVMAG-006-015 (Mixed materials 6, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-03-1978-01-04; WJZ-EVMAG-009-002 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-04; WJZ-EVMAG-009-003 (Mixed materials X, Tape x)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-04; WJZ-EVMAG-009-003 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 3)
    - Bunny Reunion, 1977-01-04; WJZ-EVMAG-009-003-01 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 3, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-04; WJZ-EVMAG-009-004 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-05; WJZ-EVMAG-009-005 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1878-01-05; WJZ-EVMAG-009-006 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 6)
    - A Day at the Races, 1978-01-05; WJZ-EVMAG-009-005-01 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-06; WJZ-EVMAG-009-007 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-09; WJZ-EVMAG-009-008 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 8)
    - Blood, Sweat, and Tears, 1978-01-09; WJZ-EVMAG-009-008-01 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 8, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-09; WJZ-EVMAG-009-009 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-10-1978-01-16; WJZ-EVMAG-009-010 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 10)
    - Appaloosa, 1978-01-10; WJZ-EVMAG-009-010-01 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 10, Segment 1)
    - Child Can't Read, 1978-01-12; WJZ-EVMAG-009-010-02 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 10, Segment 2)
    - Undercover Traffic Cops, 1978-01-16; WJZ-EVMAG-009-010-03 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 10, Segment 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-11; WJZ-EVMAG-009-011 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 11)
    - Super Cue, 1978-01-11; WJZ-EVMAG-009-011-01 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 11, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-12; WJZ-EVMAG-009-012 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-13; WJZ-EVMAG-009-013 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-13-1978-01-17; WJZ-EVMAG-009-014 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 14)
    - Intensive Care For Kids, 1978-01-13; WJZ-EVMAG-009-014-01 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 14, Segment 1)
    - Law for Sale, 1978-01-17; WJZ-EVMAG-009-014-02 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 14, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-01-16; WJZ-EVMAG-009-015 (Mixed materials 9, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-02-09-1978-02-16; WJZ-EVMAG-011-009 (Mixed materials 11, Tape 9)
    - Making Of TV Spot, 1978-02-09; WJZ-EVMAG-011-009-01 (Mixed materials 11, Tape 9, Segment 1)
    - Alan Christian, 1978-02-16; WJZ-EVMAG-011-009-02 (Mixed materials 11, Tape 9, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-02-16; WJZ-EVMAG-011-x (Mixed materials x, Tape x)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-02-09; WJZ-EVMAG-011-010 (Mixed materials 11, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-02-10-1978-02-14; WJZ-EVMAG-011-011 (Mixed materials 11, Tape 11)
    - Love In The 70's, 1978-02-10; WJZ-EVMAG-011-011-01 (Mixed materials 11, Tape 11, Segment 1)
    - Starland Vocal Band, 1978-02-14; WJZ-EVMAG-011-011-02 (Mixed materials 11, Tape 11, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-02-10; WJZ-EVMAG-011-012 (Mixed materials 11, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-02-13-1978-02-17; WJZ-EVMAG-011-013 (Mixed materials 11, Tape 13)
    - Linnea At 90, 1978-02-13; WJZ-EVMAG-011-013-01 (Mixed materials 11, Tape data_value_missing_6ba497924f4bb3a101b8085b9061dbb6, Segment 1)
    - Blind Leading The Sighted, 1978-02-17; WJZ-EVAG-011-013-02 (Mixed materials 11, Tape 13, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-02-13; WJZ-EVMAG-011-014 (Mixed materials 11, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-03-01-1978-03-06; WJZ-EVMAG-012-013 (Mixed materials 12, Tape 13)
    - Husband Beating, 1978-03-01; WJZ-EVMAG-012-013-01 (Mixed materials 12, Tape 13, Segment 1)
    - Randy Newman, 1978-03-06; WJZ-EVMAG-012-013-02 (Mixed materials 12, Tape 13, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-03-06; WJZ-EVMAG-012-x (Mixed materials x, Tape x)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-03-02; WJZ-EVMAG-012-014 (Mixed materials 12, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-05-01-1978-05-05; WJZ-EVMAG-016-003 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 3)
    - We Make $12 A Day, 1978-05-05; WJZ-EVMAG-016-003-01 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 3, Segment 1)
    - Operation Mind Control, 1978-05-01; WJZ-EVMAG-016-003-02 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 3, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-05-01; WJZ-EVMAG-016-x (Mixed materials x, Tape x)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-05-03-1978-05-10; WJZ-EVMAG-016-004 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 4)
    - Get Anything Without Money, 1978-05-03; WJZ-EVMAG-016-004-01 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 4, Segment 1)
    - The Kennedy Cup, 1978-05-10; WJZ-EVMAG-016-004-02 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 4, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-05-04-1978-05-05; WJZ-EVMAG-016-005 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-05-08; WJZ-EVMAG-016-006 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 6)
    - Behind Covent Walls, 1978-05-08; WJZ-EVMAG-016-006-01 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-05-08; WJZ-EVMAG-016-007 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-05-09-1978-05-17; WJZ-EVMAG-016-008 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 8)
    - The Alien Factor, 1978-05-09; WJZ-EVMAG-016-008-01 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 8, Segment 1)
    - Palmistry, 1978-05-19; WJZ-EVMAG-016-008-02 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 8, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-05-11; WJZ-EVMAG-016-010 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 10)
    - Baltimore Best Bowlers, 1978-05-11; WJZ-EVMAG-016-010-01 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 10, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-05-09-1978-05-10; WJZ-EVMAG-016-009 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-05-11-1978-05-12; WJZ-EVMAG-016-011 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-05-12; WJZ-EVMAG-016-012 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 12)
    - Klaus Wagner's 125hour Kiss, 1978-05-12; WJZ-EVMAG-016-012-01 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 12, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-05-15-1978-05-16; WJZ-EVMAG-016-013 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 13)
    - Brooks, 1978-05-15; WJZ-EVMAG-016-013-01 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 13, Segment 1)
    - Rolfing, 1978-05-16; G-016-013-02 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 13, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-05-15; WJZ-EVMAG-016-014 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 14)
    - Brooks Robinson, 1978-05-15; WJZ-EVMAG-016-014-01 (Mixed materials 16, Tape 14, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-25-1978-07-27; WJZ-EVMAG-021-002 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 2)
    - Junk Food, Champagne Balloon Of Light, 1978-07-26; WJZ-EVMAG-021-002-01 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 2, Segment 1)
    - Fruit Salad, Italian Festival + Free Operation, Salt Water For Bad Breath, 1978-07-27; WJZ-EVMAG-021-002-02 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 2, Segment 2)
    - Shady Towns, Dorsey Speedway, 1978-07-25; WJZ-EVMAG-021-002-03 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 2, Segment 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-25-1978-07-27; WJZ-EVMAG-021-x (Mixed materials x, Tape x)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-26; WJZ-EVMAG-021-003 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 3)
    - Richest Yacht, 1978-07-26; WJZ-EVMAG-021-003-01 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 3, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-27; WJZ-EVMAG-021-004 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 4)
    - Bob Turks Forecasts, 1978-07-27; WJZ-EVMAG-021-004-01 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 4, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-27-1978-07-28; WJZ-EVMAG-021-005 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-28; WJZ-EVMAG-021-006 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 6)
    - Frisbee Superstars, 1978-07-28; WJZ-EVMAG-021-006-01 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-31; WJZ-EVMAG-021-007 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 7)
    - The Last Manned Lighthouse On The Bay, 1978-07-31; WJZ-EVMAG-021-007-01 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 7, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-31-1978-08-01; WJZ-EVMAG-021-008 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-31-1978-08-03; WJZ-EVMAG-021-009 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 9)
    - Poison Ivy, Fitness Trial, Shabazz Bakery, 1978-07-31; WJZ-EVMAG-021-009-01 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 9, Segment 1)
    - Dog Birth Control, No Fish Today, Knees, Bike Shop, 1978-08-02; WJZ-EVMAG-021-009-02 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 9, Segment 2)
    - Fish Barbeque, Weekend Afram, Pregnancy Test, Frame Shop, 1978-08-03; WJZ-EVMAG-021-009-03 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 9, Segment 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-01; WJZ-EVMAG-021-010 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 10)
    - Don't Let The Swarm Get You, 1978-08-01; WJZ-EVMAG-021-010-01 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 10, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-02; WJZ-EVMAG-021-011 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 11)
    - Raising Daisy Our Baby Giraffe, 1978-08-02; WJZ-EVMAG-021-011-01 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 11, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-02-1978-08-03; WJZ-EVMAG-021-012 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-04-1978-08-07; WJZ-EVMAG-021-013 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-10-1978-08-11; WJZ-EVMAG-021-014 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-11; WJZ-EVMAG-021-x (Mixed materials x, Tape x)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-10-1978-08-16; WJZ-EVMAG-021-015 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 15)
    - Bean Salad, Fake Plants, 1978-08-10; WJZ-EVMAG-021-015-01 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 15, Segment 1)
    - Worming, Bounty, Diet-Arteries, 1978-08-16; WJZ-EVMAG-021-015-02 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 15, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-14-1978-08-15; WJZ-EVMAG-021-016 (Mixed materials 21, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-13-1978-07-17; WJZ-EVMAG-023-003 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 3)
    - Saul Good And Bowling, 1978-07-13; WJZ-EVMAG-023-003-01 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 3, Segment 1)
    - Stuff Shoulder Of Lamb, 1978-07-14; WJZ-EVMAG-023-003-02 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 3, Segment 2)
    - Garden Going To Seed, 1978-07-17; WJZ-EVMAG-023-003-03 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 3, Segment 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-07-17; WJZ-EVMAG-023-x (Mixed materials x, Tape x)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-08-31-1978-09-01; WJZ-EVMAG-023-004 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-05; WJZ-EVMAG-023-005 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 5)
    - Birthday Special, 1978-09-05; WJZ-EVMAG-023-005-01 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-05; WJZ-EVMAG-023-006 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 6)
    - Evening's Anniversary, 1978-09-05; WJZ-EVMAG-023-006-01 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-07; WJZ-EVMAG-023-007 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 7)
    - Mom I'm Leaving Home, 1978-09-07; WJZ-EVMAG-023-007-01 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 7, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-07-1978-09-08; WJZ-EVMAG-023-008 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-08-1978-09-11; WJZ-EVMAG-023-009 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1978-09-08; WJZ-EVMAG-023-010 (Mixed materials 23, Tape 10)